Engineering and Applied Sciences, College of; Records ua670
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Records, 2000-2015; 2; 15 cubic ft.
  - IBM Research, 2007-2008 (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 6)
  - IBM Resources, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 7)
  - FMR Executive Board, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 8)
  - FMT, 2008 (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 9)
  - Ice Gov Brochure, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 10)
  - IFMR Conference, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - IFMR Working Group, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 12)
  - IFW, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 13)
  - IMLS, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 14)
  - IMLS Diversity Proposal, 2009 (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 15)
  - INF Proposal, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 16)
  - Informatics, 2005 (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 17)
  - Informatics, 2006-2009 (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 18)
  - Informatics - B.S. Degree, 2014 (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 19)
  - Informatics Course Action Forms, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 20)
  - Informatics, Doctoral Program Review, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 21)
  - Informatics Meeting, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 22)
  - Informatics Ph.D., Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 23)
  - Informatics Ph.D. Admissions, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 24)
  - Informatics (INF)-Ph.D., Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 25)
  - Informatics Ph.D. Student, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 26)
  - Informatics The New School Org Chart, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 27)
  - Information Science BA, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 28)
  - Informatics (INF)-Space, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 29)
  - Informatics Task force, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 30)
  - Informatics Redesign, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 31)
  - INF Retreat, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 32)
  - INF Scheduling Requests, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 33)
  - Information Science General, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 34)
  - Information Science PACIST Report, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 35)
  - Information Science Planning Documents, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 36)
  - Information Science Provosts Advisory Committee, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 37)
  - Information Security, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 38)
  - Information Studies, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 39)
  - Information Studies, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 40)
  - Information Studies, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
  - Information Studies (Course Action Forms), Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
  - Info Studies Retreat, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 3)
  - Info Studies, 2012 (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 4)
  - Information Studies Ph.D. Program, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 5)
  - Information Studies Provosts Advisory Committee, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 6)
  - Information Studies School Library Media, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 7)
  - Information Studies Provosts Advisory Committee, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 8)
  - Information Studies -Course Action, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 9)
  - Infrasim, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 10)
  - Infrasim Resources, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - Infrasim - Simulation Day, 2002 October (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 12)
  - International Sematech, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 13)
  - Intiatives for Women (IFW), ca. 1998 (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 14)
  - International, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 15)
  - International Education Appointee, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 16)
  - Student Profiles, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 17)
  - Ankara University, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 18)
  - Delegation, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 19)
  - International Education Committee, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 20)
  - IST, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 21)
  - IST Accreditation, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 22)
  - IST Course Planning, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 23)
  - IST General Information, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 24)
  - IST Hiring Plans, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 25)
  - IST Internship, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 26)
  - IST423 (temp until 01/2007), 2007 January (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 27)
  - IT/CCI Task force, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 28)
  - IT Commons, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 29)
  - IT Commons, 2004-2005 (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 30)
  - ITC Academics, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 31)
  - IT Commons Background, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 32)
  - IT Commons Committee Resources, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 33)
  - IT Commons Course Catalog, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 34)
  - IT Commons Development, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 35)
  - IT Commons External Constituents for Development, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 36)
  - IT Commons Faculty, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 37)
  - IT Commons Faculty RPF, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 38)
  - IT Commons Handouts, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 39)
  - ITC Hires, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 40)
  - IT Commons Management Group, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 41)
  - IT Commons MOU - Computer Science, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 42)
  - IT Commons Personnel Art/Music, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 43)
  - IT Commons Personnel Computer Science, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 44)
  - IT Commons Personnel Criminal Justice, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 45)
  - IT Commons Personnel Economics, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 46)
  - IT Commons Personnel ETAP, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 47)
  - IT Commons Personnel Geography and Planning, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 48)
  - IT Commons Personnel Information Science, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 49)
  - IT Commons Personnel Physics/Biology, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 50)
  - IT Commons Personnel Political Science, Undated (Box 8 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 51)
  - IT Commons Personnel Public Administration, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
  - IT Commons Pictures, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
  - IT Commons Searches, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 3)
  - IT Commons Steering Committee, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 4)
  - IT Commons Survey, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 5)
  - IT Commons Three-Ring, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 6)
  - IT Commons UPC, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 7)
  - IT Learning, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 8)
  - IT Commons Search, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 9)
  - ITC Course Catalog, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 10)
  - ITC Faculty Recruit, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - IT Dean Meetings, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 12)
  - IT Services, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 13)
  - IT Workforce, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 14)
  - IT Dean Meetings, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 15)
  - IT Services, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 16)
  - IFMR Active, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 17)
  - IMFR, 2009 (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 18)
  - Jones Trinity Alliance, 2010-2013 (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 19)
  - Judaic Studies, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 20)
  - Junior First League LEGO, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 21)
  - Kaplan Foundations Sheila Kaplan, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 22)
  - LAAP, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 23)
  - Legal, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 24)
  - Legislative Initiative, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 25)
  - Steven Levy, 2012 (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 26)
  - Librarianship (Excellence), Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 27)
  - Library Programs Symposium, 2014 October 9 (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 28)
  - Library Renovation, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 29)
  - Library University Libraries Newsletter, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 30)
  - Making It Real Part II, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 31)
  - Massoni, Al, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 32)
  - Mission Review II, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 33)
  - Mementos, Undated (Box 9 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 34)
  - MOUs, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
  - Navitas, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
  - NCWIT, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 3)
  - NERFI, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 4)
  - NERFI Joint Proposal, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 5)
  - New College, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 6)
  - New College Joan, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 7)
  - New College Resolution, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 8)
  - New File-Health IT, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 9)
  - News Letter, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 10)
  - Newit Scorecard, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - New York State Central Accounting System Need Analysis, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 12)
  - NIJ Elect Crimes Partnership, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 13)
  - NSA CAE/IAE, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 14)
  - NSF CPATH Proposal, 2009 (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 15)
  - NSF Day, 2011 (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 16)
  - NSF ISCC Workshop, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 17)
  - NSF ITR Proposal, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 18)
  - NSF Scholarships for Service 2001 Proposal (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 19)
  - NSF SFS Copies, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 20)
  - NSF SFS Grant, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 21)
  - NTCIR, 2012 (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 22)
  - NTCIR, 2009 (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 23)
  - NTCIR conference, 2006 (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 24)
  - NTIR New Trends in Informatics Research Conference, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 25)
  - NYS Cyber Security Conference, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 26)
  - NYSERnet, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 27)
  - NYSL New York State Library, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 28)
  - NYS Public Sector Academy, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 29)
  - NYSTAR, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 30)
  - NYSTAR Proposal, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 31)
  - NYS OFT/CIO Workforce, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 32)
  - NYS Writer's Institute, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 33)
  - NY CIO Academy Advisory Board, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 34)
  - NYCWIT, 2013 (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 35)
  - NY CIO Academy, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 36)
  - NY CIO Academy Advisory Board, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 37)
  - NY Opportunity Online Broadband Summit, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 38)
  - NY Wired for Education, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 39)
  - NYLA, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 40)
  - NYLA Online Course, 2012 Spring (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 41)
  - NYPTI, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 42)
  - NYS Broadband Council, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 43)
  - NYS DOH - Ozlem Uzuner/Jim Dias, Undated (Box 10 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 44)
  - NYS Forum, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
  - NYS Grid, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
  - NYSUNY 2020, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 3)
  - NYS IT Workforce, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 4)
  - NYSP & OFT Support, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 5)
  - Moving Notes, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 6)
  - ODK, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 7)
  - Office of International Education, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 8)
  - OLeary Professorship, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 9)
  - Online Teaching & Learning, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 10)
  - Online Learning, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - Open Source Festival, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 12)
  - Lego, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 13)
  - Lego, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 14)
  - PEAC, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 15)
  - PEAC-E, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 16)
  - Performance Dashboard, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 17)
  - PFI, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 18)
  - PhD Student, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 19)
  - Philips Sue, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 20)
  - Policy Lunch, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 21)
  - Pre-Proposal Purdue, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 22)
  - Presentations DGI, 2000 June 7 (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 23)
  - Presentations - ITC External, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 24)
  - Presentations President Ryan, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 25)
  - President Hall, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 26)
  - President Hall Meeting, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 27)
  - President Jones (Robert), Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 28)
  - Planning for meeting, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 29)
  - President Jones Inauguration, 2013 (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 30)
  - Tutu Sisters, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 31)
  - President Jones UAlbany Vision, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 32)
  - Proposal DOL, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 33)
  - Proposal IGERT Pre-Proposal, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 34)
  - Props, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 35)
  - Provost, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 36)
  - Provosts Assessment Symposium, 2013 (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 37)
  - Provost's Executive Advisory Council, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 38)
  - Provost Advisory Report, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 39)
  - Public Relations, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 40)
  - Public Security Certificate, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 41)
  - Purdue - CERIAS Affiliation, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 42)
  - Purdue - CERIAS - LAAP, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 43)
  - Recommendation Letters, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 44)
  - Research Benchmark, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 45)
  - Research-Hot Topics, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 46)
  - Research, Office for, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 47)
  - Research Reports, 2011-2012; 2012-2013; 2013-2014 (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 48)
  - RPI-Proposal for Regional Node Porgram (1-Corps Node), Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 49)
  - Rockefeller College, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 50)
  - Rockefeller College Dean Search, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 51)
  - Rules and Regulations Committee, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 52)
  - Salient, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 53)
  - SCLA, Undated (Box 11 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 54)
  - School of Public Health, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
  - Security Dynamics Network, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
  - SEC-Consolidated Audit Trail, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 3)
  - Selective Investment, 2006-2007 (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 4)
  - SEMATECH project, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 5)
  - Seven to Al Mussoni, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 6)
  - SIRF, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 7)
  - SISP, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 8)
  - smAlbany, 2013 (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 9)
  - Social Robotics, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 10)
  - Software Alliance Troy, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - Space, 2014 (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 12)
  - Space CCI Student CTR, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 13)
  - Space Issues, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 14)
  - Space Needs, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 15)
  - Space Planning, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 16)
  - Space Requests-INF, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 17)
  - SPWG Strategic Planning Working Group, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 18)
  - Staff Meetings, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 19)
  - Stallman, Richard, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 20)
  - Statistics, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 21)
  - STRAP Proposal ESDC, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 22)
  - Strategic Planning Committee, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 23)
  - Strategic Plan-It, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 24)
  - Student Actions, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 25)
  - Student Center, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 26)
  - Student Evaluations, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 27)
  - Summer Retreat, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 28)
  - Student Success, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 29)
  - Social Welfare, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 30)
  - SS, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 31)
  - SQL Saturday, 2015 July 25 (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 32)
  - Summer Sessions, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 33)
  - SunGard Colleges Report, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 34)
  - SUNY-Business & Education Leadership, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 35)
  - SUNY Central, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 36)
  - SUNY- Central Cyber Security, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 37)
  - SUNY Empire Innovation Program, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 38)
  - SUNY High Needs, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 39)
  - SUNY International, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 40)
  - SUNY Korea, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 41)
  - SUNY Leadership Conference, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 42)
  - SUNY Learning Network, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 43)
  - SWIFT, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 44)
  - Teachapalooza, 2012 (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 45)
  - Techapalooza, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 46)
  - Tech Valley Code Camp, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 47)
  - Tech Valley High School, Undated (Box 12 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 48)
  - TechConnex, Undated (Box 13 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
  - Technology Needs, Undated (Box 13 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
  - TERA Grid Proposal, Undated (Box 13 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 3)
  - TVHS Project, Undated (Box 13 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 4)
  - UAlbany Day, 2009 (Box 13 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 5)
  - UAlbany Impact, 2020 (Box 13 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 6)
  - Ualbany Strategic Planning, Undated (Box 13 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 7)
  - UG Office Grand Opening, Undated (Box 13 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 8)
  - University Library Renovation, Undated (Box 13 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 9)
  - University Senate, Undated (Box 13 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 10)
  - University of Laval- Quebec, Canada, Undated (Box 13 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - UPC-University Planning and Policy Council, Undated (Box 13 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 12)
  - Urban Research and Outreach Engagement, Undated (Box 13 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 13)
  - URPAC, Undated (Box 14 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
  - Utica-Rome, Undated (Box 14 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
  - UUP Discretionary Raises, Undated (Box 14 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 3)
  - UUP Salary Listing, Undated (Box 14 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 4)
  - U.S. News, Undated (Box 14 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 5)
  - Vaio-Laptop, Undated (Box 14 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 6)
  - Washington, University of, Undated (Box 14 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 7)
  - Watervliet Innovation Center, Undated (Box 14 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 8)
  - WEB, Undated (Box 14 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 9)
  - Webmasters Guild, Undated (Box 14 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 10)
  - Wii Current, Undated (Box 14 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - Workstudy, Undated (Box 14 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 12)
  - Women Studies, Undated (Box 14 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 13)
  - Working Groups, Undated (Box 14 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 14)
  - WSIS, Undated (Box 14 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 15)
  - Zogby International, Undated (Box 14 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 16)
  - The IACE Application For Accreditation of Information Assurance, 2004 (Box 15 (2-Administrative Records), Item 1)
  - College-Wide Handouts, Undated (Box 15 (2-Administrative Records), Item 2)
  - Advisory Workgroup, 2008 (Box 15 (2-Administrative Records), Item 3)